So if you want to feel really sad about
the human race right now and you are in
the UK, uh go to the App Store and go to
the chart of uh the top free apps. When
you're there, you'll discover that uh
Grok, which is the AI tool based off of
uh Elon Musk's X, is currently in second
place, which in normal times would be
just like hey, whatever, cool. Um I
think ChatGPT is number one.
>> [music]
>> So another AI being second uh should be
fine. Uh other than the fact that the
only reason that people are currently
talking about Grok and Grok is currently
in the news is that uh Grok has been
shown to be able to be used uh to
non-consensually uh remove clothes in
photos. And I think when I learned that
there had been a sizable number of
people whose response to that news story
had been to download Grok, uh I sort of
felt deeply sad on um the uh just very
deep uh level. And in fact, um I kind of
want to propose a test, right? And that
is that uh you go to your friends and
you ask them to uh show you uh the App
Store on uh their phones. And if it
shows that they have never downloaded uh
Grok, uh that's cool. You you continue
to be friends with them. Um if, however,
it shows anything uh other than the like
uh get thing and it has the like
redownload option or maybe they've
already got it on their phones, uh
you you might want to have some serious
conversations with that friend.